<MsgFile>
  <Msg>
    <Id>1</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>NO_ROUTE_KEEPIN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>No route keepin.</Desc>
    <ExtDesc>The route engine needs to have a route keepin shape defined to
 determine the area where routing can be added. The route keepin may or 
 may not be the same as the board outline. If no route keepin is defined,
 the size of the Allegro drawing is used. To avoid this warning, create a 
 route keepin shape.
     </ExtDesc>    
     <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>2</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>NO_PINS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>No pins found.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>No pins where found on any component. Check that the correct
	design has been loaded and that there is at least one component with at
	least one pin placed in the design.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>3</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>NO_ENABLED_NETS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>No nets enabled for routing.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>Either no nets were found in the design, or all nets in the design
    have been disabled for routing. Check that some nets are route enabled.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>4</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PIN_OUTSIDE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>Pin {1} is outside the route keepin.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>This pin is on an unplaced component, or the component
    has not been placed within the route keepin shape. Check the location
    of the pin and that its component has been placed.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>5</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PIN_SURROUNDED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>Pin {1} is completely enclosed by route keepouts on all layers.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>Each pad on each layer of the design is blocked for routing.
    The route engine is unable to route to this pin. Check for the ability to
	route to this pin using interactive etch edit mode.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>6</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PIN_NO_FANOUT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>Surface mount pin {1} has no fanout.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>This pin is defined on only one layer but is not routed to a through hole via. 
	The route engine requires that all pins are fanned out prior to routing.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>7</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>NET_NO_LAYER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>Net {1} has no layers on which routing is enabled.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>This net is blocked from routing on all layers. Verify that this net
    can be routed in Allegro using interactive etch edit mode. Verify that the layer
    stackup allows routing on at least one layer.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>8</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PIN_UNLOCKED_FANOUT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>Surface mount pin {1} has unlocked fanout.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>This pin has been fanned out but the fanout via has not 
    been locked (fixed). The route engine may delete this via preventing a
    route to the pin. To avoid this warning, lock the via.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>9</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DELAY_MISMATCH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>Match or relative delay constraint defined on {1} for match group {2}
	is defined in units of {3} for delta and {4} for tolerance. This is
	inconsistent with other relative delay constraints on the same match group.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>Delay constraints can be specified in terms of time, length, or percentage.  
    All delay constraints specified on elements of a specific match group must all be 
	defined in the same terms (for example, all in terms of time). Members of match groups 
	must be defined using the same units.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>10</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>TOTAL_ETCH_LENGTH_NO_MATE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>Total etch length is defined on {1} but not on {2}, which is its
	differential pair mate.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>Members of the same differential pair should have the same constraints.
    For this differential pair, a total etch length constraint was defined on one
    member but not the other.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>11</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>TOTAL_ETCH_LENGTH_MIS_MATCH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>Total etch length defined on {1} does not match total etch length
	defined on {2}, which is its differential pair mate.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>Members of the same differential pair should have the same constraints.
    For this differential pair, the total etch length constraint defined on one
    member of the differential pair is different from the total etch length constraint
    defined on the other member of the differential pair.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>12</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PROP_DELAY_NO_MATE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>Prop delay is defined on {1} but not on {2}, which is its differential pair mate.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>Members of the same differential pair should have the same constraints.
    For this differential pair, a propagation delay constraint was defined on one
    member, but not the other.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>13</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>AUTOBUNDLE_SUCCESS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>Autobundle completed successfully.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>This is a normal status message indicating that the route engine has
	automatically created one or more bundles.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>14</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>AUTOBUNDLE_FAILURE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>Autobundle failed to complete.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>A problem occurred while the route engine was trying to create bundles.
	Select fewer rats to bundle, or create the bundles interactively.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>15</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DIFF_PAIR_GAP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>Differential pair {1} has a primary gap or neck gap set to zero.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>A differential pair constraint has been defined, but either a primary gap
	or a neck gap was not defined. Check that both a primary gap and neck gap are 
	specified on all layers, or that neither a primary gap nor a neck gap is specified.</ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>16</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>MXL_INFO</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>Status message reporting normal operation.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>This is a normal status report generated automatically. It can be
	safely ignored.</ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
  <Id>17</Id> 
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>FLOWLINE_UNDER_COMP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME> 
  <Category>W</Category>
  <Desc>Flow line of bundle {1} ends underneath component.</Desc>
  <ExtDesc>Part of the flow for this bundle is under a component. To allow the route engine
  maximum flexibility to find paths under components, place the flow and its rake area
  outside all component outlines.</ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>18</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>LARGE_PIN_COUNT_NET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>W</Category> 
  <Desc>Net {1} contains {2} pins and is not marked as a VOLTAGE net therefore all
   connections will be scheduled for routing.</Desc>
  <ExtDesc>Extended description</ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>19</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>FLOW_OUTSIDE_ROUTE_KEEPIN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>W</Category> 
  <Desc>Flow of bundle {1} is outside route keepin.</Desc>
  <ExtDesc>Extended description</ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>20</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>RDM2ALDB_SKIPPED_RATS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>W</Category> 
  <Desc>Rats were skipped that could not be processed for the current command. See GRE log file for details.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc> Commit plan and convert to plan commands are unable to process rats
  that do not meet certain criteria such as plan level. For example, commit
  plan requires that the plan have a minimum plan level of topological.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>21</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_SELECTION_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>E</Category> 
  <Desc> The GRE selection required for '%s' failed and the command cannot run.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  The current command needed to pass element selections along to the GRE
routing engine to control the scope of its activity. This selection failed.
The current command will not proceed because the selection failure would
cause the route engine to act on the entire design.
Contact Cadence customer support for assistance.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>22</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_EXECUTE_CMD_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>E</Category> 
  <Desc> GRE execute command failed. The GRE log file may have more details.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  A GRE command was required as part of the current command, but the command
had an unexpected failure. Contact Cadence customer support for assistance.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>23</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_SPAWN_CMD_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>E</Category> 
  <Desc> GRE spawn command failed. The GRE log file may have more details.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  A GRE command was required as part of the current command, but the command
had an unexpected failure. Contact Cadence customer support for assistance.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>24</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_AUTOBUNDLE_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>E</Category> 
  <Desc> GRE autobundle failed. The GRE log file may have more details.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  The GRE autobundle command ran into an unexpected error.
Contact Cadence customer support for assistance.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>25</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_STRATEGY_VERSION_MISMATCH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>E</Category> 
  <Desc>
  GRE stragegy file version mismatch. The GRE log file may have more details.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  The runtime environment has a GRE strategy file that is a different version
than is expected for product version that is running. GRE based commmands
cannot be run. Remove local copies of strategy.dat and strategy.tcl.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>26</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_CMD_INVALID_WHILE_PLANNING</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>E</Category> 
  <Desc> This command cannot be run while GRE is planning.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  An attempt was made to run a command that cannot be run while planning is
active. This is an unexpected situation.
Contact Cadence customer support for assistance.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>27</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_TILING_FAILURE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>E</Category> 
  <Desc> GRE initialization failed. The GRE log file may have more details.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  GRE initialization is required to prepare for planning and other GRE commands.
Failures are unexpected. Contact Cadence customer support for assistance.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>28</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_RESELECTION_INCOMPLETE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>W</Category> 
  <Desc> Some GRE objects could not be selected.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  The current action needed to pass element selections along to the GRE
routing engine to control the scope of its activity. This selection was
not completely successful, causing some objects to not be selected. The
action continued with the selections that were successful. This is likely
to have some impact on the result of the action.
The GRE log file may have more details on the failure.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>29</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_NOEDIT_IBD_RATBUNDLE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>W</Category> 
  <Desc> %s cannot modify interface ratbundles.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  An attempt was made to run a ratbundle delete or edit command with
an interface ratbundle in the selection set. Interface ratbundles are
auto-generated and cannot be direcly modified by this command.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>30</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>GRE_NORENAME_IBD_RATBUNDLE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>W</Category> 
  <Desc> Interface ratbundles cannot be renamed.
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  Interface ratbundles are auto-generated and given a name based on the 
net group or bus that was used to group the ratnests. This name can only
be modified by renaming the net group or bus.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output> 
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
  <Id>31</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>AIDT_RETURN_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>E</Category>
  <Desc> Errors encountered. %s
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc>
  Auto interactive Delay Tune command encountered some error conditions.
The GRE log file may have more details on encountered errors.
  </ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>
  <Msg>

  <Id>32</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>AIDT_RETURN_STATISTICS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>I
    <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
  </Category>
  <Desc> Clines Selected: %d; Timing constraints: %d; Timing violations: %d; Outside ideal range: %d
  </Desc>
  <ExtDesc></ExtDesc>
  <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

</MsgFile>

    
