<MsgFile>

  <Msg>
    <Id>1</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_UNABLE_OPEN_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create log file. Check directory access permissions and available disk space.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>2</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_BEGIN_CREATE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Beginning creation of %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>3</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_CREATE_SUCCESS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Creation successful.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>4</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_CREATE_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Creation failed -- see log file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>5</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_WRONGFORMAT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Wrong input format. Either some fields are missing or are in wrong order.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>6</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_USER_CANCEL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
User interrupted creation of new component and symbol.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>7</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>TILEMSG_NO_ATTACHMENT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to read configuration data for tile. Tile must be uprevved to current database revision. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>8</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>TILEMSG_NO_MEMORY</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Tiling unable to allocate all required memory. Increase system memory or swap file size.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>9</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>TILEMSG_NO_TEMP_FILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Tiling unable to create necessary temp file. Check temp file directory is writable and disk is not full.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>10</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTOWMSG_SINGLE_ITEM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Automatically selecting only eligible %s (%s).
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
There is only one placed component of the specified type in the design. To save time,
the tool automatically selected this component for export.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>11</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTOWMSG_NO_ITEMS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Design contains no %s components eligible for export. Only placed components may be exported.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Because the die and BGA text files define both logical and physical information, 
you can export only the  placed components that have an associated symbol instance. 
To export an unplaced component, first place it somewhere in the physical drawing 
layout and run the Die Text-Out wizard again.

If the database has a placed component of the correct type, use the show element 
command to check the component class of the item that you are exporting. The 
component class must be &quot;IO&quot; for BGA components and &quot;IC&quot; for die components.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>12</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTOWMSG_FINISHED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s Text-out Wizard completed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>13</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTOWMSG_CANCELLED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s Text-out Wizard cancelled.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>14</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTWOMSG_NO_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create log file. Check directory access permissions and available disk space.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>15</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTOWMSG_SCRIBE_VALUES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Scribe line information was exported for this symbol.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Scribe line information affects the size of the die symbol. It is the difference between 
the drawn die in an IC layout tool and the size of the manufactured component after it 
has been cut from the wafer using a scribing process. 
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>16</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTOWMSG_SHRUNKEN_SYMBOL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
An optical shrink was applied to the exported symbol. 
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
When importing a die component, this tool is able to apply an optical shrink to 
the physical symbol definition. This will cause all pieces of the symbol 
definition to be shrunk by the percentage specified. This can lead to multiple 
original values mapping to the same value because of the numerical scaling and 
maximum database accuracy. 
 
Due to this potential for rounding and numerical conversion errors, the die symbol 
will be exported as it is currently represented in the database (after the optical 
shrink). If this component is read into another package design, do not apply the 
optical shrink again.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>17</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_FINISHED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s completed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>18</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_CANCELLED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s cancelled.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>19</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_NO_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create log file. Check directory access permissions and available disk space.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>20</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_NO_FILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
No source file was selected for data import. Select a file to proceed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>21</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_EMPTY_FILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The text file selected for import is empty. There is nothing to process.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>22</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_BAD_UNITS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
%s is not a recognized units string for length measurement.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Because this tool accepts only the following units of measurement: 
   mils, inches, millimeters, centimeters, and microns, 
the value specified in the file will be ignored. Select the appropriate 
units in the wizard before importing data.   
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>23</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_AUTO_HEADER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Text file contains a column header line. This has been used to pre-configure the columns for import.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>24</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_NOT_A_NUMBER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The value in the highlighted cell must be a numeric value.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The value in the highlighted cell must be a numeric value based on the data type 
currently configured for this column. Correct the error in the text file or 
mark the row or column containing this cell to be ignored and proceed.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>25</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_NOT_A_PINUSE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Specified pin use not recognized. 
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Every pin use must be one of the following strings:
    UNKNOWN, UNSPEC, POWER, GROUND, NC, IN, OUT, BI, TRI, OCA, OCL
If the data file is incorrect, exit the wizard and correct the data file. Else, 
mark this row of the file to be ignored and continue.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>26</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_BAD_CELL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The highlighted cell does not meet the requirements for the column header type.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
To correct this error, perform one of the following tasks:
   1. Change the column header type if it was configured incorrectly by the tool. 
   2. Ignore this row if it represents a comment or data that should not be imported.
   3. Exit the wizard and edit the text file to correct the data.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>27</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_DUPLICATE_PIN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Duplicate pin numbers found. The first duplicate pin number has been highlighted.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Each physical pin number must be unique within a component definition or 
symbol definition. Duplicate pin numbers are not allowed. 

Correct this situation as follows:
  1. If this is a result of a line occurring twice in your file, mark the second
     line to be ignored by placing an &apos;x&apos; in the first column for the line. 
  2. If a pin number is used twice for two different physical pins,
     exit the wizard and change the data file, then run the wizard again.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>28</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_MEASURE_BAD_STRING</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The value entered could not be converted into a length measurement.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>29</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_MEASURE_TOO_SMALL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The value entered is too small. The value must be at least %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>30</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_MEASURE_TOO_LARGE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The value entered is too large. The value cannot exceed %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>31</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_DESIGN_TOO_SMALL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The pins do not fit within the current design extents. Use Setup -&gt; Design Parameter Editor -&gt; Design to enlarge the design.  
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
You cannot place a symbol in the drawing if it does not fit within the 
current drawing extents. Correct this problem by enlarging the drawing 
size and importing the text file again.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>32</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_EXTENTS_ADJUST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Adjusting %s of symbol extents to fit within the design extents.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
You must place a  symbol instance in the design so that the entire symbol fits 
within the specified drawing extents. The current origin value, symbol extents, and 
drawing extents combination do not meet this criteria, so the symbol origin has 
been adjusted automatically.    
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>33</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_PIN_EXTENTS_ADJUST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Adjusting %s of symbol extents to encompass all pins in file.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
A symbol definition&apos;s extents must completely enclose all pin origins specified for the 
symbol. The current value for this field is less than the required value; therefore, 
it has been enlarged to meet this criteria.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>34</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_ORIGIN_ADJUST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Adjusting %s coordinate of symbol origin to fit symbol within the design extents.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
You must place a symbol instance in the design so that the entire symbol is completely 
within the specified drawing extents. The current origin value, symbol extents, and 
drawing extents combination do not meet these criteria, so the symbol origin has been 
adjusted automatically.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>35</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_DIMENSION_ADJUST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Adjusting %s to encompass all pins.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The extents of a symbol definition must completely enclose all pin locations specified 
for the symbol. The current value for this field is would result in one or more pins 
residing outside the proposed extents. This value has been modified to the minimum 
legal value.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>36</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_VALUE_ADJUST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
The value changed from %s to %s.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The original value for this field required adjustment to ensure that the resulting 
symbol definition would meet the necessary database requirements.  The symbol definition 
must encompass all pins of the symbol and the symbol must be located within the extents 
of the current drawing.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>37</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_DUPLICATE_NAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The symbol name is already in use. This value must be unique across all symbol definitions in the design. Enter another name.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>38</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_DUPLICATE_REFDES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The reference designator is already in use. This value must be unique across all component instances in the design. Enter another value.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>39</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_USER_CANCEL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
The user interrupted the data import process.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
If you click the &quot;&apos;stop&quot; button during the import of a text file, the process
is interrupted so that you can regain control of the system. Text files, 
even large files, import quickly. If the import takes a long time, the database 
may not be configured correctly for the chosen text file.

If your file import is taking a long time, check the following:
   1. Pin-to-pin DRC spacing requirements are set to values that are 
      compatible with the data being imported.
   2. The correct database units were selected on the first page of 
      the wizard. Set the units to those of the text file, not of the
      destination database, and the tool will perform any numerical conversions.
   3. If padstacks are referenced from the current database or library, the 
      existing padstack definition may not be compatible with the file being 
      imported. 
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>40</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_IMPORT_WARNINGS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The data import completed, but with warnings. See the log file for details.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>41</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_IMPORT_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The data import failed. See the log file for details.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>42</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_IMPORT_SUCCESS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
The data import successfully completed. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>43</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_BEGIN_IMPORT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Beginning import of data. This may take some time.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>44</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_SCROLL_TO_VALUE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The cell with the error has been highlighted in red on row %d.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>45</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_BLANK_FIRST_NET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The first net name field is blank. Pins will be assigned to dummy net.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
If you do not provide a net name for the first row of the net list text file, 
the tool does not consider this an error. Instead, the tool assumes that the 
pin should be assigned to a dummy net in the system.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>46</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_BAD_SCRIBE_DIMENSION</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Illegal scribe value for %s side. Value must be greater than or equal to 0.0.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The scribe values define the remaining material after a die has been cut from the 
wafer in the die manufacturing process. You cannot use a negative value because 
it would imply that the scribing action removed material from the manufactured 
die component.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>47</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_INVALID_GRID</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The file contains invalid pin grid definitions. These grids will be ignored.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The die and BGA text files contain specialized lines, usually at the bottom of 
the file, which define the pin-editing grid structures that are created for use 
in the Die and BGA editor environments. 

These lines are written by the tool on a text export and may not be edited by 
the user. 

To correct this problem, load the symbol into the appropriate editor after 
completing your text file import, and reconstruct the missing grids.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>48</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_GRID_BAD_FORMAT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Ignoring the pin grid definition on line %ld because it is incorrectly formatted.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The die and BGA text files contain specialized lines, usually at the bottom of 
the file, which define the pin-editing grid structures that are created for use 
in the Die and BGA editor environments. 

These lines are written by the tool on a text export and may not be edited by 
the user. 

To correct this problem, load the symbol into the appropriate editor after 
completing your text file import, and reconstruct the missing grids.
    </ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>49</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_GRID_INVALID_EXTENTS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Ignoring the pin grid definition on line %ld because it is has invalid extents. 
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The die and BGA text files contain specialized lines, usually at the bottom of 
the file, which define the pin-editing grid structures that are created for use 
in the Die and BGA editor environments. 

These lines are written by the tool on a text export and may not be edited by 
the user. 

To correct this problem, load the symbol into the appropriate editor after 
completing your text file import, and reconstruct the missing grids.
    </ExtDesc>    
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>50</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_PINS_ADDING_NETS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Attaching pins to their nets (creating new nets as required).
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>51</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_SCRIBE_ADDED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
A scribe width of %s was added to the %s side of the symbol definition.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>52</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_SHRINK_APPLIED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
An optical die shrink of %f percent was applied to the symbol definition.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>53</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_MISSING_PIN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to find pin %s.%s. The pin was not added to net %s.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
This error typically occurs when the case of the pin number referenced 
in the text file does not match the pin number in the database 
to which it refers.  

For example, in a column that specifies case-sensitive names, 
&quot;a1&quot; does not match &quot;A1&quot;.      
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>54</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_PIN_ON_DUMMY_NET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Pin %s.%s was placed on a dummy net.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>55</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_PIN_ON_REAL_NET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Pin %s.%s was added to net %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>56</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_UNABLE_CREATE_NET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create a new net named %s.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The net name requested contains illegal characters.  Consult your 
documentation for a complete list of legal characters for net names.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>57</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_CREATED_NEW_NET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Created new net %s from net name %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>58</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_NO_ATTR_DEF</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to find the definition for the %s property named %s in the current design.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The system was unable to find the referenced property definition. This 
occurs in one of two circumstances:
  1. The reference is to an obsolete system property. Most often, this is caused
     by a property reference from a file originally constructed in an earlier release. 
     Remove or update the reference to the property definition.
  2. The reference is to a user-defined property. The user-defined 
     property is not yet defined in the active database. Define the property, then 
     import the file again. 
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>59</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_NO_ATTR_CREATE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to add the property %s with the value %s to %s %s.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
When a property cannot be added to an object in the system, it is due to 
one of the following:
   1. The property is not legal for use on the selected object type. 
      In this case, the reference to the property in the file being 
      imported should be removed. 
   2. The value supplied is badly formatted or outside the allowed
      range for the specified property definition. Modify the value
      and import  the file again.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>60</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_ATTR_CREATED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Added the property %s with the value %s to %s %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>61</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_CREATING_OBJECT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Beginning creation of %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>62</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_NO_DEVICE_FILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to write the device file for component. Check directory-access permissions and available disk space.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Usually, you are unable to write a device file because of a read-only file system or a 
lack of sufficient free disk space for the file that you are creating. Note that device 
files require that a minimum of two pins is  present in the component definition. 
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>63</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_CREATION_SUCCESS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s creation completed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>64</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_CREATION_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s creation failed. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>65</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_PINS_CREATED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The following symbol pins were created (coordinates relative to symbol origin):
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>66</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_NETS_COMPLETE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Net attachment phase completed%s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>67</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_PINS_ADDING_PROPS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Adding required pin and net properties.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>68</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_ADDING_PROPS_COMPLETE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Property attachment phase completed%s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>69</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_MISSING_COLS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
These required columns are missing: %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>70</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_UNMATCHED_COLS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
These columns must always be present in matched pairs: %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>71</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_PLACEHOLDER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
This message is a placeholder for a message which does not exist yet. (no arguments)
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>72</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_PLACEHOLDER1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
This message is a placeholder for a message which does not exist yet. (1 argument: &apos;%s&apos;)
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>73</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_PLACEHOLDER2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
This message is a placeholder for a message which does not exist yet. (2 arguments: &apos;%s&apos;, &apos;%s&apos;)
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>74</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_PLACEHOLDER3</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
This message is a placeholder for a message which does not exist yet. (3 arguments: &apos;%s&apos;, &apos;%s&apos;, &apos;%s&apos;)
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>75</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_TO_CONTINUE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to continue refreshing via structures.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>76</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_START_ONE_REFRESH1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Attempting to refresh via structure &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>77</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_COMPLETED_VS_REPLACE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Completed refreshing all via structures successfully.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>78</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_ONE_WARNING</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Completed refreshing via structures, but there was one warning and therefore there may be one or more unrefreshed via structures. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>79</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_SOME_WARNINGS1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Completed refreshing via structures, but there were %s warnings and therefore there may be one or more unrefreshed via structures. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>80</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_ONE_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to complete refreshing via structures.  There was 1 error encountered.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>81</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_SOME_ERRORS1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to complete refreshing via structures.  There were %s errors encountered.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>82</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_SYMFILE_MISSING1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
When trying to open a file containing a list of via structures to refresh, unable to locate or open list file &apos;%s&apos; for reading.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>83</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_NO_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create log file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>84</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_OPTIONS_HDR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
------ Via Structure Refresh Options ------
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>85</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_INPUT_FILE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
INPUT DESIGN FILE = &apos;%s&apos;
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>86</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_OUTPUT_FILE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
OUTPUT DESIGN FILE = &apos;%s&apos;
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>87</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_DESIGN_FILE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
DESIGN FILE = &apos;%s&apos;
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>88</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_LISTFILE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
VIA STRUCTURE LIST FILE  = &apos;%s&apos;
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>89</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_IGNOREFIXED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
IGNORING FIXED VIAS
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>90</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_PADPATH_HDR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
------ Library Paths ------
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>91</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_NO_PADPATH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
PADPATH Environment Variable is not set or has no entries.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>92</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_PADPATH_A1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
PADPATH = %s
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>93</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_PADPATH_B1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
-&gt;        %s
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>94</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_MESSAGES_HDR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
------ Via Structure Refresh Messages ------
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>95</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_IN_DESIGN_HDR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
------ Via Structures in Input Design Database ------
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>96</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_SYMDEF_NAME1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>97</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_TO_REFRESH1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
------ Via Structures Listed for Refresh in %s ------
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>98</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_BUILD_SYMDEF_LIST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to build a list of Via Structure definitions in the current design, probably a memory allocation problem.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>99</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VIA_STRUCT_START</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Attempting to refresh via structure &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>100</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VIA_STRUCT_DONE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Completed refreshing via structure &apos;%s&apos; successfully.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>101</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_NO_LIB_VIA_STRUCT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to find via structure, &apos;%s&apos;, in library directory search path. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>102</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_FAILED_VS_REPLACE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to complete refreshing via structures.  Errors detected.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>103</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_WARN_VS_REPLACE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
There are some via structures which cannot be refreshed. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>104</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UPDATE_VIA_STRUCT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to refresh Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; due to the above warning(s) and/or error(s).
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>105</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_NOVS_FOUND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
No via structures found or selected.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>106</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_NO_SYM_NAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
No symbol name found.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>107</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_FIXEDPROP_INST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; has an instance with the FIXED property.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>108</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_NONVS_INST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; has an instance which does not seem to be a via structure.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>109</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_PART_TILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; has an instance that is part of a tile.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>110</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_NO_MATCH_START_LAYER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Layer &apos;%s&apos; does not match the old via structure starting layer.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>111</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_NO_START_LAYER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is not correctly connected to a pin/via.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>112</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_MISSING_IN_NEW</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; is found in the database, but is missing from the library. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>113</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_MISSING_IN_OLD</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; is found in the library, but is missing from the database. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>114</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NOOLDVS1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; is not in the database.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>115</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_OLDNOTDEF3</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; not on &apos;%s&apos; pin &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>116</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NONEWVS1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; is not in the database or the library.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>117</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_DNFRMDB</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Done, updated via structure.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>118</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NOUPDATE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
No via structure updated, check parameters.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>119</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_SAMNMERR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Symbol, Pin, RefDes and Net must be &apos;*&apos; when old and new names are the same.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>120</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NOSYMBOL1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
This is an invalid selection as the symbol &apos;%s&apos; is not in the database or is not directly connected to the old via structure.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>121</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NOPNONSY2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
This is an invalid selection as there are no instances of &apos;%s&apos; directly connected to &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>122</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NOPINS3</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Via structure &apos;%s&apos; with symbol &apos;%s&apos; is not on &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>123</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NOREFDES1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
This is an invalid selection as the symbol with refdes &apos;%s&apos; is not in the database or is not directly connected to the old via structure.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>124</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NONET2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Net &apos;%s&apos; does not match via structure &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>125</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NOOLD_NEWVS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
One of the old via structure or the new via structure is NULL.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>126</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_SYS_ATTR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Cannot find via structure attribute in the system.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>127</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_END</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
------ End of Refresh Via Structure ------
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>128</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_XML_FILE_NOT_FOUND1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to find an XML file in the library path for Via Structure &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>129</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_DUMMY_SYMDEF1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create a dummy symdef for the new version of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>130</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_XML_PARSER_ERROR1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The XML Parser was unable to build a new symdef for Via Structure &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>131</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_DEFINST_CHECK_FAILS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Checking definition and instances of Via Structure fails.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>132</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_ADD_LAYER_LIST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to add a layer number to a layer list because of memory allocation issues.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>133</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_BUILD_LAYER_LIST1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to build a layer list for symdef of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>134</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_SINGLE_INST_CHECK_FAILS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Via Structure Instance Check failed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>135</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_NON_VS2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Instance of symbol &apos;%s&apos; at location &apos;%s&apos; is not a Via Structure.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>136</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_IS_FIXED2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Instance of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; at location &apos;%s&apos; has the FIXED property.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>137</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_CHILD_IS_FIXED2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
A child of the instance of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; at location &apos;%s&apos; has the FIXED property.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>138</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_VS_IS_IN_TILE2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Instance of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; at location &apos;%s&apos; is part of a TILE group.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>139</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_SYMINST_NO_ELEMENT2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to find the first element connected to the instance of symbol &apos;%s&apos; at location &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>140</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_SYMINST_INVALID_START2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Instance of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; at location &apos;%s&apos; has an invalid start element.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>141</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_SYMINST_LAYER_MISMATCH2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Instance of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; at location &apos;%s&apos; does not match the new via structure start layers.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>142</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_ADD_ELEM_LIST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to add an element to an element list because of memory allocation issues.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>143</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_NULL_SYMDEF</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
NULL symbol definition was passed to Via Structure Refresh routine.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>144</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_NULL_SYMDEF_NAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The symbol definition passed to Via Structure Refresh routine has an invalid symbol_name.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>145</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_BUILD_INST_LIST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to build a list of Via Structure instances because of memory allocation issues.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>146</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_USING_XML2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Using XML file &apos;%s&apos; to generate new symbol for Via Structure &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>147</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_NEW_SYMDEF</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to a symbol definition from an XML file for the new version of Via Structure.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>148</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_CURRENT_DEF_NAME1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The current Via Structure definition name is &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>149</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_INST_AND_TILE_NAMES2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Instance of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; is part of tile group &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>150</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_REM_INST_TILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to remove a Via Structure instance from the Tile Group it belonged to.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>151</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_INST_AND_LOCATION2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
There is an instance of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; at location &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>152</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_DELETE_INST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to delete a Via Structure instance.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>153</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_DELETE_DEF</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to delete a Via Structure definition.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>154</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_CREATE_INST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to create a refreshed Via Structure instance.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>155</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_ADD_TO_GROUP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to add a refreshed Via Structure instance back to its Tile Group.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>156</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_SET_FIXED_PROP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to set the FIXED property on a refreshed Via Structure instance.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>157</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_TO_DELETE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to delete Via Structure&apos;s instances and definition.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>158</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_TO_REFRESH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to refresh the Via Structure.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>159</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_REFRESH_COUNT2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Refresh of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; complete, &apos;%s&apos; instances have been refreshed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>160</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_ABS_REL_PATH_FAILURE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to find absolute .lef path from relative path %s when preparing to read CML file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>161</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_BUFINIT_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Initialization of buffer by bufinit failed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>162</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_BUFPEND_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to add an item to a buffer.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>163</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CANT_CREATE_UNIQUE_REFDES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create unique refdes.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>164</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_CASEIDERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. The NAMESCASESENSITVE statement is missing.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>165</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_ENDIDERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. Unexpected termination of the file occured.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>166</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_ENDOFFILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. End of file encountered.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>167</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_EXTENTSIDERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. Expected EXTENTS identifier as argument #1 on line.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>168</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_FILEIDERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. There was no LEF file path specified. Syntax error on line.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>169</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_LAYEROPTIONSERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. There is a LAYER options mismatch.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>170</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_LOW_MEMORY</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. LOW MEMORY problem.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>171</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_MACROIDERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. Expected MACRO identifier as argument #1 on line.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>172</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_NOPINSDEFINEDERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. There were no PINS defined.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>173</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_SITEIDERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. There was a SITE field missing on line.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>174</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CML_VERSIONERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error during read of CML file. The version of the CML file does not match.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>175</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_COMP_DEF_FAILURE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failure during creation of Component Definition from Library data.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>176</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_CREATE_DRIVER_FAILURE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to create driver instance.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>177</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DEF_CML_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failure during reading of LEF/CML file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>178</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DEF_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failure during LEF/DEF import.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>179</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DEF_INVALID_DEF_FILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid DEF file name.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>180</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DEF_INVALID_LIB_NAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Lef file not found at path specified in the ldf file. DEF import terminated
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>181</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DEF_NO_PINS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
No pins encountered during reading of LEF/CML file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>182</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DEF_NO_REQ_LAYERS_DEFINED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Required layers not defined in LEF/CML file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>183</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DEF_PARSER_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Parser error during reading of LEF/CML file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>184</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DRV_CASESENS_ERR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The NAMESCASESENSITIVE value is not the same for all CML files.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>185</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DRV_FAIL_READ_CML</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failure during read of Driver data from CML file(s).
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>186</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DRV_LEF_DB_SYM_FAIL3</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Database function %s failed for symbol for driver %s%s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>187</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DRV_LEF_FAIL_NAMECHK2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
%s name %s fails Allegro Database check for valid names.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>188</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DRV_LEF_UTL_COM_FAIL3</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Utility function %s failed for component for driver %s%s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>189</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DRV_NO_CML2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
No CML file %s for library %s. Use LEF library manager to generate one.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>190</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DRV_NO_LIB_LEF</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Can&apos;t load Driver data because selected .ldf file points to no LEF file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>191</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DRV_NO_LIB_SELECTED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Can&apos;t load Driver data from LEF/CML file(s) because no .ldf file is selected.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>192</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_DRV_PROBLEM_WITH_CML</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failure during checking of CML file(s) prior to reading Driver data.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>193</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_FAIL_GROUP_ADD2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to add %s to %sgroup (Die, Tile, ...).
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>194</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_LEFPARSERERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Parser error during reading of LEF/CML file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>195</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_LEF_REQUIRED_CML_MISSING</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
A required .cml file is missing.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>196</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_NO_APP_MACROS_IN_LEF</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
No appropriate macros encountered during reading of LEF/CML file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>197</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_NO_LDF_IN_CWD</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
There is no .ldf file in the current working directory.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>198</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_NO_LEF_MACRO1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
No IC Library macro exists for driver %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>199</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_PADSTACKNAME_FAILURE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to create new valid padstack name.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>200</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_PADSTACK_CREATION_FAIL2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create padstack for pin %s of driver %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>201</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_PIN_PROCESS_FAIL1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Processing of symbol pins failed for driver %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>202</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_READONLYDIR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
A required .cml file was not created as the directory is read only, DEF import terminated.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>203</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_SYMALLOC_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Allocation of memory by SYMalloc failed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>204</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_SYM_DEF_FAILURE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failure during creation of Symbol Definition from LEF/CML data.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>205</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_USERABORT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
A required .cml file was not created due to the User Abort. LEF Processing.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>206</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_NULL_PARAMETER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Parameter(s) can not be NULL.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>207</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_NO_LEF_MACRO</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
No IC Library macro %s exists.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>208</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_PIN_PROCESS_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Driver pin process failed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>209</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CIOMSG_PADSTACK_CREATION_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Padstack creation failed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>210</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PADMSG_PADSTACKNAME_UNIQUE_FAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error creating unique padstack name.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>211</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PADMSG_CONDUCTOR_LAYER_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error creating pad on conductor layer. Check layer stackup.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>212</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PADMSG_PPIN_LAYER_MAPPING_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error finding mapped layer for layer %s defined for physical pin. Check layer mapping.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>213</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PADMSG_PAD_LAYER_MAPPING_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error finding mapped layer for layer %s defined for pad. Check layer mapping.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>214</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PADMSG_WIREBOND_LAYER_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error creating pad on bonding wire layer. Check layer stackup.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>215</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PADMSG_RDL_LAYER_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error creating pad on routing layer. Check layer mapping or pad layer(s) in the CML file(s).
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>216</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_INVALID_DEST_DB</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid destination database specified for co-design component import.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>217</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_INVALID_SOURCE_DB</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid source database specified for co-design component import.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>218</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_INVALID_SOURCE_COMP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid source component supplied. Will attempt to locate desired comp automatically.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>219</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_INVALID_DB_CODES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid source-destination database types supplied to co-design component interface.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>220</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_INVALID_ORIGIN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid origin point specified for co-design component. Origin outside design extents.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>221</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_DUPLICATE_REFDES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Desired co-design component refdes already exists in design.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>222</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_BAD_EXISTING_ELEM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid handle specified for co-design component/symbol to replace. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>223</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_UNKNOWN_MAPPING</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unrecognized co-design component import mapping provided. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>224</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_MISSING_DEFS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Source design does not contain the necessary component and symbol definitions.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>225</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_BAD_PADSTACK</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Source design symbol is not a single-layer component. Check padstacks after importing.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>226</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CCDMSG_USER_CANCEL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Update of co-design component cancelled by user.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>227</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_FINISHED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Import co-design die command finished. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>228</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_CANCELLED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Import co-design die command cancelled. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>229</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_NO_COMP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Source design does not contain required die component instance or definition.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>230</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_NO_SYMBOL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Source design does not contain required die symbol instance or definition.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>231</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_NO_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create log file for command. Possible read-only directory.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>232</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_NO_FORM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to open form file. Possibly corrupt environment.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>233</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_DUPLICATE_REFDES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Reference Designator already in use. Choose another.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>234</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_DUPLICATE_DEVICE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Device name already exists in design from alternate codesign die.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>235</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_DUPLICATE_PACKAGE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Package name already exists in design from alternate codesign die.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>236</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_MEASURE_BAD_STRING</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The units string is not valid. Either the units is not recognized or the value is out of range. Check that the units format is correct, and that the value is in a correct range.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>237</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_MEASURE_TOO_SMALL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid entry. Value must be at least %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>238</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_MEASURE_TOO_LARGE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid entry. Value must be at most %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>239</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_NO_FORM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to open form file. Possibly corrupt environment.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>240</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>UCDMSG_NO_FORM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to open form file. Possibly corrupt environment.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>241</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>UCDMSG_NO_CODESIGN_DIES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Design contains no co-design die instances. Nothing to update.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>242</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>UCDMSG_SELECT_COMPONENT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Select the die instance to be used for updating definition.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>243</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>UCDMSG_CLOSE_PLANNER_WINDOW</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Close I/O Planner view of definition, then attempt update again.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>244</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>UCDMSG_NO_UPDATE_IN_SIP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Update codesign die command is unnecessary in the Cadence I/O Planner environment and should not be used.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>245</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSTKMSG_BAD_STACK_NAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid die stack name provided. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>246</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSTKMSG_GROUP_NOT_FOUND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Die stack group not found.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>247</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSTKMSG_STACK_EXISTS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Stack name already exists in design. Name must be unique.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>248</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSTKMSG_STACK_NOT_EMPTY</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to delete die stack. Stack is not empty.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>249</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSTKMSG_WRONG_GROUP_TYPE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Group supplied is not a die stack group.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>250</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSTKMSG_BAD_COMPONENT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid die component. Cannot be added to die stack group.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>251</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSTKMSG_DIFFERENT_GROUPS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Previous die belongs to different group than requested for new die. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>252</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DEGASMSG_SHAPE_TOO_SMALL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Degassing Failed - Shape too small.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>253</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DEGASMSG_POLYCREATION_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to create polygon for obstacle within shape.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>254</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_NOT_VALID_INT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Value %s is not a valid integer.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>255</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_STRING_TOO_LONG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The %s has been truncated due to its length.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>256</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_NO_FILENAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to read file. No file name was supplied.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>257</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_CANNOT_FIND_FILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to locate file %s. Ensure the file exists and is readable.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>258</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_XML_INIT_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
XML Initialization failed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>259</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_INVALID_XML</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid XML file. The file contains one or more syntax errors.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>260</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_BAD_IMPORT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
XML Parser error encountered: %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>261</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_BAD_IMPORT_CAUSE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Most likely cause of error: %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>262</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_MPS_COMMAND_RUNNING</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to update database. Exit the current command and update package from the 3D viewer again.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>263</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_MPS_CANT_FIND_ITEM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to locate item to update. The item may have been deleted from database after the 3D viewer was launched.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>264</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_MPS_CANT_CREATE_DRC</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create DRC marker in database. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>265</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_MPS_BAD_DIAMETER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to modify bond wire&apos;s diameter. Diameter must be greater than 0.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>266</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_MPS_BAD_PROFILE_NAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create wire profile definition. No profile name was supplied.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>267</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_MPS_BAD_PROFILE_POINTS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to modify profile definition. The list of points defining the wire is invalid.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>268</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSAMSG_BAD_ARGS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Bad argument passed to DSA API - contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>269</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSAMSG_BAD_STACK</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Error processing die stack. Contact Cadence customer support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>270</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSAMSG_UNPLACED_DIE_EXTENTS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Symbol extents were requested for an unplaced die.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>271</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DIEREPMSG_NOT_CACHED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Attempt to perform die replace without proper data cache.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>272</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPPADMSG_ILLEGAL_INPUT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid object type passed to GetPadstackLayer.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>273</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPPADMSG_NO_PAD_FOUND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
No satisfying pad found on layer type specified.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>274</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_INVALID_PARAM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Invalid parameter passed to ICP utility API -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>275</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_BAD_WIRE_LAYER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Wire group refers to bonding wire layer name (%s) that no longer exists or has changed layer type. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>276</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_BAD_WIRE_LAYER_RECOVER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Resetting to first bonding wire layer in design (%s). Use the wirebond modify groups command to reset to the desired new layer.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>277</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_DIEPROPERTIES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Die Properties
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>278</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_CHG_DISCARDED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The changes to the scribe line were discarded.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>279</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_CHG_APPLIED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The changes to the scribe line were applied.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>280</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_CHANGED4</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The %s scribe for die %s was changed from %s to %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>281</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_ORIENT_NORTH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
north
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>282</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_ORIENT_SOUTH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
south
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>283</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_ORIENT_EAST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
east
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>284</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_ORIENT_WEST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
west
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>285</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_ZERO_UM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
0 UM
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>286</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_SCRIBEREMOVED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The scribe line was removed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>287</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_ADDDEFAULTLIB_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not add a default library or cell due to invalid parameter passed -- contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>288</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_BLANKLIBS_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not blank the libraries due to invalid parameter passed -- contact Customer Support. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>289</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_BROWSEDEF_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not check OpenAccess library definition file due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>290</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_BROWSEVER_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not check verilog file due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>291</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_BROWSELIBDEFS_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not browse for the OpenAccess library definition file due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>292</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_CHECKDEF_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not check DEF file due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>293</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_CHECKVER_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not check Verilog file due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>294</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_CHECKLIBDEFS_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not check the OpenAccess library definition file due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>295</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_CHKDUPVIEW_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not check for duplicate view.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>296</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_DEF_BROWSE_CANCEL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not open file using file browser. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>297</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_DEF_FILE_DOESNT_EXIST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
DEF file does not exist. Check whether path or file does not exist.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>298</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_DIR_NOT_READABLE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Directory specified is not readable. Check directory permissions for read access.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>299</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_DIR_NOT_WRITEABLE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Directory specified is not writable. Check directory permissions for write access.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>300</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_DRAWING_NAME_TOO_LONG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Name exceeds drawing name maximum lengths. Verify that Library, Cell, and file base names do not exceed maximum lengths.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>301</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_DUPLICATE_VIEW</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Duplicate View for current library/cell found.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>302</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_FILE_NOT_READABLE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
File specified could not be opened for reading. Check file permissions for read access.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>303</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_FILE_NOT_WRITEABLE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
File specified could not be opened for writing. Check file permissions for write access.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>304</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_FORM_CREATE_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not create Add Codesign Form. Check memory usage.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>305</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_ILLEGAL_FILENAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
File name specified is not in proper format. Enter more than one valid character for file name.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>306</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_INIT_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not initialize form fields data. Global libraries do not exist  -- Contact Customer Support. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>307</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_LEFLIB_NOT_SETUP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
IC Library Manager not set up.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>308</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_LIBCELLVIEW_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not read in Library/Cell/Views due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>309</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_LIST_CREATION_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not create list of popup entries due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>310</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_NOLEFLIBMGR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
IC Library Manager not configured. Check whether IC Library Manager can be invoked. If not, contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>311</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_NO_UPDATES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not update form fields due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>312</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_POPUPLIST_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not add entries to popup fields. Check memory usage, and whether popup form is present.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>313</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_SETCURRENTPOP_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not set the current library/cell/view entry due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>314</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_DEFBROWSE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Could not open DEF file for reading.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>315</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_VERBROWSE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Could not open Verilog file for reading.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>316</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_DEFILETOLOAD</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Enter name of DEF file to load
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>317</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_VERFILETOLOAD</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Enter name of Verilog file to load
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>318</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_DUPLAYOUTVIEW</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Could not create device as Library/Cell has an already defined view by same name.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>319</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_LEFSNOTSET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
LEF files have not been set up using Library Manager.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>320</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_LIBDEFS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Could not open the OA library definition file for reading and writing.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>321</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_LIBDEFSFILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Select library definitions file
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>322</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_LIBDEFSFILT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Library Definitions File |*.defs|
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>323</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UPDATECELL_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not update the cells in popup list due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>324</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UPDATELIB_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not update the librarys in popup list due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>325</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UPDATEVIEW_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not update the views in popup list due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>326</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_UNIQUE_STRING_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not create unique symbol definition string due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>327</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_UNIQUE_SYMBOLDEF</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not create unique symbol definition. Placement on cursor failed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>328</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_SYMBOL_DEFINITION</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not create symbol definition. Placement on cursor failed. Verify proper symbol extents from imported die.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>329</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_NO_ICPARM_RECORD</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not retrieve IC Parameter record for placed die. Editing die failed. Verify SiP file for integrity.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>330</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_NO_GROUP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not retrieve group name for placed die.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>331</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_ZOOMONREFDES_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not zoom to placed symbol due to invalid parameter passed -- Contact Customer Support.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>332</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_UIF_READLIBDOTDEFS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Reading the OpenAccess library definition file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>333</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_UIF_FINISHLIBDOTDEFS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Finished reading the OpenAccess library definition file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>334</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_OAGETLIBS_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not retrieve library information from the OpenAccess library definition file. Check that the OpenAccess libraries are loaded, and the OpenAccess library definition is not corrupted.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>335</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_OAINGETOAINFO_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not retrieve OA library information for lib/cell/view specified. Check that the OpenAccess libraries are loaded, and the OpenAccess library definition is not corrupted.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>336</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_NO_DIE_SYMBOL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not create symbol instance for cursor placement.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>337</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_OAINPROCESSOADATA_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not import die from OA. Check oaImport log file for further error message details.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>338</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_VERILOG_FILEOPEN_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not open Verilog file for reading. Check file permissions for read access.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>339</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_DEFREADER_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
A parser error occured while reading the DEF file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>340</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_RECT_SYMDEF_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not attach a rectangle to the symbol definition. Placement on cursor failed. Verify proper symbol extents from imported die.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>341</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_REFDES_PLACEMENT_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not attach refdes to symbol definition.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>342</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_CREATELEFSTRING_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not initialize LEF files for invoking Encounter from SiP. Check memory usage, and whether IC Library Manager can be invoked.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>343</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_REL_TO_ABS_PATH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not convert from relative path to absolute path.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>344</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_LIBCELLVIEW_NOT_UNIQUE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Library/cell/view must not already exist to proceed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>345</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_BLANK_REFDES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not place device with blank reference designator field. Enter a reference designator and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>346</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_ENC_TCL_OSRELTOABSPATH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not convert relative path to absolute path in order to prepare command file for Encounter. Check directory paths.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>347</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_TEMP_FILE_WRITE_OPEN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not open temporary file for writing. Check temporary file and directory permissions for write access.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>348</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_FILE_OPEN_READ_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not open the OpenAccess library definition file for reading. Check directory and file permissions for read access.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>349</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_REFDES_ILLEGAL_OA_CHARS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Refdes contains one or more invalid OA characters:  , / : [ ] #. Enter a refdes without these characters.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>350</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_TEMP_VIEW</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
sipTempView cannot be used for view, as it cannot be edited.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>351</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_IOP_ENVVAR_USED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Using environment variable for IOP initialization command during scripting playback.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>352</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_ITEM_TYPE_NOT_SUPPORTED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The object type %s is not supported for querying by _icpIsItemType.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>353</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_RES_TYPE_NOT_SUPPORTED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The object type %s is not supported for querying by _icp_getSubclassesByRestriction.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>354</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_IOP_CELLNAME_CHANGED2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
IOP has changed the OA cell name from %s to %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
    <Id>355</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPUTL_PARENT_LOG_OPEN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Log file already opened by parent command. Appending to existing log.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
    <Id>356</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPUTL_UNABLE_OPEN_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to open requested log file: %s.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Probable causes for inability to open a log file include:
  1. Specified directory for log file has read-only permissions. 
     To correct, check and reset access permissions for the directory.
  2. Disk is full. No space left to create new file handle. 
     To correct, delete some files and run the command again.
  3. Maximum number of simultaneously open file handles reached. 
     Close some currently open files or applications to free up handles.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>357</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPUTL_LOG_NO_TITLE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
No title provided for log file %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
    <Id>358</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPUTL_UNABLE_VIEW_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to open log file for viewing. No log file is open, and no log file has been previously registered.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>359</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_MCM_TO_SIP_NAG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
MCM Import generates a new SIP design from an MCM. For data changes, see extended help.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
WARNING: The MCM Import command will create a new SIP design based on the
selected MCM database. It does not import into your current design. 

During this process, die stacks will be created and all dies added to appropriate 
stack groups. If not already configured, you will be asked to define the starting
and ending layer for your package substrate, with any die layers existing outside
the substrate boundary. Full details of any conversions performed will be detailed 
in the log file.

Do you wish to proceed?
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>360</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_BRD_TO_MCM_NAG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
BRD Import generates a new MCM design from a BRD. For data changes, see extended help.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
WARNING: The BRD Import command will create a new MCM design based on the
selected BRD database. It does not import into your current design.

Through this conversion process, objects may be modified to convert them from valid
PCB design objects into package objects. Unsupported objects will not be permitted
through the conversion process. Full details will be provided in the log file after 
your conversion is performed.  

If not already configured, you will be asked to set up your top and bottom
substrate layers before proceeding further.

Do you wish to proceed?
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>361</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_SIP_TO_MCM_NAG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
MCM Export generates a new MCM design from a SIP. For data changes, see extended help.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
WARNING: The MCM Export command will create a new MCM design based on the
active SIP database; it does not incrementally update an existing MCM.

This process will remove all die stacks from the SIP drawing. If the design
contains more than one die stack with multiple dies or contains any 
interposer or spacer components, will not be able to export an MCM database. 
Full details of any conversions performed will be detailed in the log file.
 
Do you wish to proceed?
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>362</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_MCM_TO_BRD_NAG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
BRD Export generates a new BRD design from a MCM. For data changes, see extended help.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
WARNING: The BRD Export command will create a new BRD design based on the
active MCM database; it does not incrementally update an existing BRD.

Through this conversion process, objects may be modified to convert them from valid
package design objects into PCB objects. Unsupported objects will not be permitted
through the conversion process. Full details will be provided in the log file after 
your conversion is performed. 

Do you wish to proceed?
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>363</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_NEW_LAYERS_SET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Default layers already set. Configuration for default drawing type not performed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>364</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_NEW_LAYERS_NO_FORM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to display New Drawing Defaults form. Check installation and menupath variable.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>365</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_NEW_LAYERS_NOADD_NET_PROP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to configure %s for net %s. Reason follows.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>366</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_NEW_LAYERS_ADD_NET_PROP</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>      
    <Desc>
%s configured for net %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>367</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_NEW_LAYERS_NOADD_NET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create new default %s net %s. Reason follows.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>368</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_NEW_LAYERS_ADD_NET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>      
    <Desc>
Created default %s net %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>369</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_NEW_LAYERS_NOSET_CNS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>      
    <Desc>
Unable to set %s layer %s constraint value. Reason follows.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>370</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_NEW_LAYERS_NOSET_ONECNS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>      
    <Desc>
Unable to set constraint value on layer %s. Reason follows.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>371</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_DEFDESIGNNAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The OA cell name was derived from the design name contained in the DEF file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>372</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_DEFBASEFILENAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The OA cell name was derived from the base name of the DEF file name.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

   <Msg>
    <Id>373</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_VERILOGLASTMODULE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The OA cell name was derived from the last module contained in the Verilog file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>374</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_UIF_VERILOGBASEFILENAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The OA cell name was derived from the base name of the Verilog file name.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>375</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_UPDATE_DIE_STACKS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Creating die stacks based on physical die placements in original design.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>376</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_UPDATE_DIE_THICKNESS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Configuring die thickness values based on data available from original database as follows:
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>377</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_UPDATE_ONE_THICKNESS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
  - %s thickness set to %s based on %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>378</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_REMOVE_DIE_STACKS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Removing die stack information from database. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>
  
   <Msg>
    <Id>379</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_UPDATE_ILLEGAL_SYM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
SIP database contains spacer and/or interposer symbols. Conversion not allowed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>380</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_UPDATE_MULTIDIE_STACK</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
SIP database contains more than one multi-die stack (die stack with height &gt; 1). Conversion not allowed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>381</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_UPDATE_LAYER_THICK</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Setting thickness of layer %s to %s to match thickness of die in die stack.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
In SIP products, multiple dies can exist at the same level above the substrate. 
For this reason, it includes a die stack editor command for managing the thickness
and other physical information about the die components. This capability is not
available in the destination product. As a result, as much as possible, this data
will be updated into the layer cross-section of the output database.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>382</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_ERR_WARN_COUNT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%d errors, %d warnings.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>383</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_CONVERT_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Conversion process encountered errors. New database not written.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>384</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_CONVERT_COMPLETED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Database type conversion completed at: %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>385</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_BRDMCM_DISABLED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Database conversion between BRD and MCM/SIP is not available in this release.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
The BRD import and export commands are currently under limited customer
beta evaluation in this release. They will be available to all customers
in the near future.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>386</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_MCM_DIE_LAYERS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Database contains one or more die type layers. Conversion not allowed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>387</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_MCM_WIREBONDS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Database contains bond wires and/or bond fingers. Conversion not allowed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>388</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_MCM_IC_GROUPS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Removing die information from database. This information will be recreated from defaults if reimported.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Package design tools such as APD and SiP require information about the chip 
orientation, die attachment type, and source IC databases. This information 
is not used or supported in PCB layout tools. It will be removed from the
database. If you import this design back into a package design tool later,
default information will be configured for any die components.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>389</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_BRD_IFP_ITEMS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Database contains IFP %s items. Conversion not allowed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>390</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_BRD_ICGROUPS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Creating dies from IC-class components using default settings.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Package design tools such as APD and SiP require information about the chip 
orientation, die attachment type, and source IC databases. This information 
has been populated in the new design based on the physical and logical 
characteristics of the source database.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>391</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_BRD_PARTITIONS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Database contains partition objects. Conversion not allowed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>392</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_SIP_TO_BRD_NAG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
BRD Export generates a new BRD design from a SIP. For data changes, see extended help.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
WARNING: The BRD Export command will create a new BRD design based on the
active SIP database; it does not incrementally update an existing BRD.

Through this conversion process, objects may be modified to convert them from valid
package design objects into PCB objects. Unsupported objects will not be permitted
through the conversion process. Full details will be provided in the log file after 
your conversion is performed.  

Do you wish to proceed?
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>393</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_BRD_TO_SIP_NAG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
BRD Import generates a new SIP design from a BRD. For data changes, see extended help.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
WARNING: The BRD Import command will create a new SIP design based on the
selected BRD database. It does not import into your current design.

Through this conversion process, objects may be modified to convert them from valid
PCB design objects into package objects. Unsupported objects will not be permitted
through the conversion process. Full details will be provided in the log file after 
your conversion is performed.  

If not already configured, you will be asked to set up your top and bottom
substrate layers before proceeding further.

Do you wish to proceed?
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>394</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_BRD_RFPCB</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Database contains RF PCB design objects. Conversion not allowed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>395</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_FIX_OBJECTS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Locking objects specific to original database type to prevent editing after conversion.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
Certain objects are not understood, and thus cannot be handled properly, by the editor
for the destination database type. As a result, these objects will be locked to prevent
their editing by that tool, to ensure that they will not be corrupted.     
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>396</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>TILEMSG_NEEDS_UPREV</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Tile %s is missing configuration information. Run uprev on the file to correct problem and re-run command. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>397</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_BAD_DIE_THICKNESS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
  - Unable to compute valid die thickness for %s. Using default value.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
    <Id>398</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_ACTION_IS_IRREVERSIBLE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
This action is irreversible. Continue?
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>399</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_CANT_FIND_SCREEN_BOUND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
GUI system is having problems figuring out the size of the form.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>400</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_UNABLE_COPY_ATTRS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
During refresh, error when attempting to copy properties from an old via structure instance to its replacement.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>401</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSMSG_NO_ENDPOINTS_RETURNED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to find endpoints of a cline.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>402</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_IMPORTNETS_WARN_MN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
WARNING: Selecting the Import net assignments option will remove all existing nets already defined in the the package design. 

Press &apos;Yes&apos; to keep this option selected, &apos;No&apos; to deselect the option. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>403</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBCHGMSG_PKG_DRCS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Removing all packaging-specific (external) DRC violation markers.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>404</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_STRATEGY_FILE_NOT_FOUND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The required strategy file could not be located for the Constraint-Driven option of the Auto Assign Net command. Make sure that TECHPATH environment variable points to a valid &apos;strategy.txt&apos; file containing the constraints and parameters.</Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>405</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_STRATEGY_FILE_NOT_READ</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The file &apos;%s&apos; was found in a TECHPATH directory, but cannot be read. Check the file and directory access permissions.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>406</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_ILLEGAL_PARAM_VALUE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The value &apos;%s&apos; specified for the parameter &apos;%s&apos; is not valid. The valid values are: %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>407</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_UNKNOWN_PARAM_OR_RULE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unrecognized parameter or rule &apos;%s&apos; provided in &apos;%s&apos;. Correct or remove the unrecognized parameter.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>408</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_ILLEGAL_RULE_COST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The weighted value &apos;%s&apos; specified for the rule &apos;%s&apos; in the file &apos;%s&apos; is not valid. A valid value is any number from 0 to 99.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>409</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_UNKNOWN_RULE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unrecognized rule &apos;%s&apos; provided in the strategy file. Correct or remove the unrecognized rule.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>410</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_STRATEGY_FILE_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The Constraint-Driven Auto Assign command is unable to continue because one or more errors were encountered during processing of the file &apos;strategy.txt&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>411</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_PARAM_NOT_FOUND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
A required parameter, &apos;%s&apos;, is not specified. Specify the parameter and its value in &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>412</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_RULE_NOT_FOUND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
A required rule, &apos;%s&apos;, is not specified. Specify the rule and its weighted value (0 to 99, inclusive) in &apos;%s&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>413</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_SUCCESS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Constraint-Driven Auto Net Assignment completed successfully.    
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>414</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_UNEXPECTED_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Constraint-Driven Auto Net Assignment encountered an unexpected error. Contact Cadence customer support.    
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>415</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Constraint-Driven Auto Net Assignment encountered errors. No assignments were made.    
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>416</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_CANCEL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Constraint-Driven Auto Net Assignment command cancelled by you.    
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>417</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_ASSIGN_STATUS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to assign %d of %d pins. See log file for complete details.   
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>418</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_ALL_ASSIGNED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
All pins were assigned.    
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>419</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_CONSTRAINT_UNMET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
%d constraints were not met. See log file for complete details.   
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>420</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_CONSTRAINT_ALLMET</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
All assignment constraints were met.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>421</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICP_AAN_LAYER_NOT_FOUND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Pin &apos;%s&apos; fans out to layer &apos;%s&apos;, which is not selected for assignment. Remove the pin from the source set or add the layer to available routing layers.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>422</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_XHATCH_FILLED_4</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%d partial voids %s in shape at %s on layer %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>423</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_XHATCH_FILLED_NOEXPAND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to created expanded polygon for shape fill. Failure in expansion.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>424</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_XHATCH_FILLED_NUMSHAPES_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Processing %d shape(s) to fill partial cross-hatching voids.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>425</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_PUN_NO_ITEMS_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
No %s found in design.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>426</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_PUN_LIST_ITEMS_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The following %s were %s:
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>427</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_PUN_ITEM_SUCCESS_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
- %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>428</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_PUN_ITEM_FAILED_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
- %s deletion failed. Reason to follow:
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>429</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_PUN_SUMMARY_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Failed to delete %d %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>430</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_PUN_VIEWLOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
See log file for complete details.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>431</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_PUN_CANCEL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s cancelled. No changes made to database.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  

  <Msg>
    <Id>432</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VIAEST_DEL_MARKERS_COMPLETED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Delete Via Markers completed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>433</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VIAEST_NO_DIE_OR_DIESTACKS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Cannot run Via Estimation.  No die or diestacks found in data.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>434</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VIAEST_CANNOT_CREATE_SUBCLASS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Cannot create subclass for Via Estimation.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>435</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VIAEST_NO_SELECTED_DIE_OR_STACK</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
No selected die or die-stack.  Cannot continue.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>436</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VIAEST_DIE_OUTLINE_NOT_FOUND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Die Outline not found.  Cannot continue.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>437</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VIAEST_CANNOT_CREATE_REPORT_FILE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Cannot create report file.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>438</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VIAEST_MUST_BE_GREATER_THAN_ZERO</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
%s must be greater than 0.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>439</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VIAEST_NO_THRU_HOLE_PADSTACKS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Cannot display padstack list.  No thru-hole padstacks found in database.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>440</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VIAEST_RUN_COMPLETED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Run Via Estimation completed.  See pop-up report for details.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>441</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_LOGICALECO_LOADOA_YESNO</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Launching Cadence IOPlanner will load the new verilog file and clear the floorplan. Do you wish to load the existing OA database instead?
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>442</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DIEREPMSG_DANGLING_WIRE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The bond wire from %s to %s is not connected on both ends. This wire must be manually corrected.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>443</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_POLYOP_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Polygon %s operation failed...
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>444</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_POLYOP_STATS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Polygon %s operation completed. Result has %d polygons with %d total holes.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>445</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_USER_CANCEL_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Creation of %s interrupted by user.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>446</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_SUCCESS_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s successfully created.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>447</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_FAILED_LOG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
%s creation failed.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>448</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_FAILED_REASON</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Reason: %s.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>449</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_DEVFILE_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to write device file for component.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>450</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_PINS_ADDED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
The following pins were added.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>451</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_PINS_ADDED2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Locations are relative to the center of the symbol.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>452</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PCKGENMSG_PINS_DETAIL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
  &quot;%s&quot; at %s
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>453</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIEPROP_SETUP_LLM</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
New library is not available. Run Setup-&gt;IC Libraries to configure the new Library file, then run this command again.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>454</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_BAD_PADNAME_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Padstack name %s defined in file is not legal. This padstack has not been created.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>455</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_PADNAME_EXISTS_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I
      <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
    </Category>
    <Desc>
Padstack name %s already exists in the current database. Using existing definition.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>456</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_PAD_BAD_SHAPE_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Padstack name %s uses unrecognized pad shape %s. This padstack has not been created.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>457</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_PAD_BAD_SIZE_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Padstack name %s has undefined width/height. This padstack has not been created.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>458</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_EXIT_CURRENT_CMD</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to update from co-design database. Exit current command and try again.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>459</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_END</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
------ End of Replace Via Structure ------
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>460</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_UPDATE_VIA_STRUCT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to Replace Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; due to the above warning(s) and/or error(s).
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>461</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NEW_NOT_SELECTED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
No new via structure was selected.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>462</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_OLD_NOT_SELECTED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
No old via structure was selected.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>463</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_WORKING</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
Replace Via Structure process has started...
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>464</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NO_XML_FOR_SYM1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to find XML file for symbol &apos;%s&apos;.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>465</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_CANT_CREATE_SYMDEF</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to create or find a Via Structure symbol def from the chosen path.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>466</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NEED_XML</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
For a &apos;Same-Name&apos; Replace, which is actually a Refresh, the &apos;New&apos; definition must come from a library (XML file).
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>467</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_SEL_METHOD</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
For a &apos;Same-Name&apos; Replace, which is actually a Refresh, the selection method must be Manual Filter, with all Filters equal to &apos;*&apos;.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>468</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_IGNORE_FIXED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
For a &apos;Same-Name&apos; Replace, when there are any FIXED instances, then the Ignore Fixed Property box must be selected.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>469</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NO_SEL_OLD1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
The selected &apos;old&apos; name &apos;%s&apos; is not in database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>470</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NO_SEL_VIA1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
The selected &apos;old&apos; name &apos;%s&apos; is not a via structure.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>471</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NO_SEL_INST1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
There are no instances of the selected &apos;old&apos; name &apos;%s&apos; in the database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>472</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NO_SEL_INST</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
There are no instances of the selected &apos;old&apos; name in the database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>473</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NO_SEL_INST_WIND</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
No instances matching the OLD name and Net Filter were found in the Select Window
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>474</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NO_VIA_DEF</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to find new via structure definition in the database or in the library. Check the spelling of the symbol name.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>475</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NEED_DRC</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
There was a physical change in the database, so a Design Rule Check is required.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>476</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_DONT_NEED_DRC</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
There was no physical change in the database, so no Design Rule Check is required.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>477</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_UNABLE_TO_REFRESH1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Failed to refresh Via Structure &apos;%s&apos; as part of the current Replace operation.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>478</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_SUCCESS1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
Successfully replaced all instances of Via Structure &apos;%s&apos;
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>479</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_BAD_REPLACE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to Replace Via Structure &apos;%s&apos;.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>480</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_BAD_REPLACE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to Replace Via Structure.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>481</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_NO_SYMDEF1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to create or find a Via Structure symbol definition for via structure &apos;%s&apos; from the chosen path.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>482</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRPMSG_WINDOW_SELECT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I</Category>
        <Desc>
Window Select the instances to be replaced.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>483</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRFMSG_FILE_NOT_WRITEABLE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
File &apos;%s.lst&apos; could not be opened for writing. Check file permissions for write access.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>484</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INCOMP_MORE_LAYERS1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an incompatible via structure because it requires more layers than available in design.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>485</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_NEG_LAYER1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid layer index because it is a negative number.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>486</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_PAD_NEG_INDEX1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid pad definition because it is a negative layer index is not allowed.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>487</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_PAD_HEIGHT_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid pad height because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>488</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_PAD_OFFSET_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid pad offset because it is an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>489</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_PAD_SHAPE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid pad shape because it is an unsupported shape type.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>490</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_PAD_WIDTH_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid pad width because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>491</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_PAD_NOT_IN_XML1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid padstack name because it is not defined in an XML file.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>492</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_PAD_NOT_ANYWHERE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid padstack name because it is not defined in the database, library, or XML file.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>493</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_SEG_END_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid segment end point because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>494</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_SEG_START_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid segment start point because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>495</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_SEG_WIDTH_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid segment width because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>496</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_SLOT_HEIGHT_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid slot height because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>497</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_SLOT_NEG_TOL_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid slot negative tolerance because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>498</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_SLOT_OFFSET_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid slot offset because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>499</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_SLOT_POS_TOL_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid slot positive tolerance because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>500</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_SLOT_WIDTH_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid slot width because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>501</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_VIA_ORIGIN_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid via origin because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>502</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_ROTATION_FMT1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
&apos;%s&apos; is an invalid via rotation because it is in an incorrect format.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>503</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_CREATE_MISMATCH_PADSTACK1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Creating padstack &apos;%s&apos;. Layers may not match the original source design.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>504</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_PAD_BAD_SIZE_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Padstack &apos;%s&apos; exists in design but does not match XML specification. Generating new padstack.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>505</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_SYMDEF_EXISTS1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Symbol definition &apos;%s&apos; already exists. Rename this via structure and re-import.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>506</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_MISMATCH_LAYERS2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The layer structures of XML (%s) and design (%s) do not match.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>507</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_UNABLE_CREATE_SYMDEF1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to create Symbol definition &apos;%s&apos;.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>508</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_UNABLE_CREATE_PADSTACK1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to create padstack &apos;%s&apos;.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>509</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_UNABLE_CREATE_PAD1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to create padstack pad for padstack &apos;%s&apos;.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>510</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_UNABLE_INIT_PADSTACK1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to initialize padstack &apos;%s&apos;.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>511</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_UNABLE_CREATE_CLINE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Creation of a cline failed.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>512</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_UNABLE_CREATE_VIA</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Creation of a via failed.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>513</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_XML_ELEMENT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The parser encountered an invalid XML data element.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>514</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_DRILL_CLR_XY</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The drill clearance is invalid because the parser was unable to parse x and y clearance values.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>515</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_LAYER_STRUCT_EMPTY</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The layer structure is invalid because it is an empty string.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>516</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_XML_LAYERS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The layer structure is invalid because the XML file&apos;s layer structures are not compatible.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>517</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_STACKUP_MISMATCH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The layer structure is invalid because the XML file&apos;s and design&apos;s stackup structures do not match.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>518</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_IN_LAYER_MISMATCH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The layer structure is invalid because the layer structure in the XML file does not match actual contents of file.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>519</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_MDRILL_COLS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The multi drill is invalid because the number of columns specified is less than 1.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>520</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_MDRILL_ROWS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The multi drill is invalid because the number of rows specified is less than 1.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>521</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_IN_PSNAME_EMPTY</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The padstack name is invalid because it is an empty string not legal.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>522</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_UNITS_EMPTY</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The units string is invalid because it is an empty string.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>523</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_INV_VSNAME_EMPTY</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The via structure name is invalid because it is an empty string.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>524</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_MEM_ALLOC_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
There was a memory allocation error.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>525</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_UNABLE_GEN_PS_NAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to generate unique padstack name.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>526</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>VSRMSG_PARSER_FAILURE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The XML parser failed to completely read the input file for reasons listed above.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>527</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>V3DMSG_VIEWER_ACTIVE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
This will close the currently active Cadence 3D Viewer window. Proceed?
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>528</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_MULTI_CODESIGN_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Co-design %s already present. Only %d is allowed in this product.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>529</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_NO_FILE_NAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Enter a co-design database file name to proceed.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>530</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_BAD_FILE_NAME_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The file name &apos;%s&apos; is not valid. Enter a valid file name for the co-design database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>531</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIE_PROP_SELECT</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Select a die to view/edit its properties.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>532</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_DIE_PROP_SCRIBES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Multiple instances of the die symbol definition exist. Do you wish to continue and update all instances with the same scribe line settings?
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>533</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>EXPCHPMSG_INVALID_COMP_DEF_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
%s is not a valid component for export. No component definition found.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>534</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>EXPCHPMSG_REFDES_NOT_FOUND_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
No component with refdes %s found in the database. Unable to export chips data.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>535</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>EXPCHPMSG_EXPORT_ALL_COMPS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Exporting chips data for all available components in the database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>536</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>EXPCHPMSG_EXPORT_ONE_COMPD_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Exporting chips data for component %s (output directory &apos;%s&apos;).
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>537</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>EXPCHPMSG_EXPORT_ONE_COMP_3</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Exporting chips data for %s (component %s, output directory &apos;%s&apos;).
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>538</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>EXPCHPMSG_NOT_DIR_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
The directory path &apos;%s&apos; does not exist. The default directory &apos;%s&apos; will be used.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>539</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>EXPCHPMSG_COMPLETE_STATUS_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
The export chips process has completed %s.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>540</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_ATTACHREMOVED_I</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
An attachment was removed from the database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>541</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_READABLE_E1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The file '%s' does not have read access, and could not be attached to the database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>542</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_EXISTINGATTCHMT_E1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not attach file '%s' to database as there is already an attachment present.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>543</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_ATTACH_E1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not attach file '%s' to the database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>544</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_ATTACHADDED_I1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
The database attachment file '%s' was added to the database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>545</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_NOATTACHMENT_E</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The database attachment was not found.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>546</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_NOTEMPORARY_E</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The temporary file name was not generated.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

  <Msg>
       <Id>547</Id>
       <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_NOEXTRACT_W1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
       <Category>W</Category>
       <Desc>
Could not extract database attachment '%s'.
       </Desc>
       <Output>C</Output>
       <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>548</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_EXTRACT_I</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
The attachment was detached from the database.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>549</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPDBATTCH_ATTACHREPLACED_I1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
The database attachment was replaced with file '%s'.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>550</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDMSG_NO_VALID_LAYER</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
Unable to create a die with this type and orientation combo as there are no legal layers to create the pads on.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>551</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_COMPLETED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Import of die footprint completed.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>552</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_MISSING_REFDES</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Reference designator is missing.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
   <Msg>
        <Id>553</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_MISSING_GROUPNAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Group name is missing.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
   <Msg>
        <Id>554</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_MISSING_DESIGNNAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The die abstract file does not contain a design name.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>555</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_DETAILS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Details of new die created:
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>556</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_REFDES1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
RefDes        :  %s
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>557</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_CHIPTYPE2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Chip Type     :  %s, %s
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>558</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_LOCATION1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Location      :  %s
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>559</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_ROTATION1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Rotation      :  %s
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>560</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_SUBCLASS1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Subclass      :  %s
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>561</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_BEGINNING</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Beginning import of co-design die component.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>562</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_LDF1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
LEF library definition file used for import: %s
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>563</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_IMPORT_LIB1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
IC library used for import: %s
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
   <Msg>
        <Id>564</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_LEFLIBRARY_CONFIG</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
The IC Library has not been set up. Use the IC Library Manager to configure it.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
   <Msg>
        <Id>565</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_MISSING_BUMPNAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
An error was detected in the die abstract file: a bump without a bump name.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>566</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_PINNAME_CHANGED2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Pin name '%s' was changed to '%s'        
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>567</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_PINNUMBER_CHANGED2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Pin number '%s' was changed to '%s'        
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>568</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_PINNUM_PROPERTY1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not preserve original pin number property for pin '%s'
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>569</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_DRVPINNAME_CHANGED2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Driver Pin name '%s' was changed to '%s'
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>570</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_DRVPINNUM_CHANGED2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
Driver Pin number '%s' was changed to '%s'
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
   <Msg>
        <Id>571</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_MISSING_DRVINSTNAME</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
An error in the die abstract file was detected: missing driver instance name and/or cell name       
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>


   <Msg>
        <Id>572</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_PACKAGENAME_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a package name for the reason above.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>573</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_INVALID_SYMDEFNAME1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a symbol definition name from name '%s'.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>
   
   <Msg>
        <Id>574</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_SYMDEFNAME_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a symbol definition name for reason above.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>575</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_INVALID_GROUPNAME1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not set the component group name based on reference designator name '%s'.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>576</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_GROUPNAME_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not set the component group name for the reason above.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>577</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_GROUP_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not add component instance or symbol instance to group for reason above.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>578</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_ICPARMERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create an IC parameter record for the component for the reason above.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>579</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_INVALID_PACKAGENAME1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a package name based on design name '%s'.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>
   
   <Msg>
        <Id>580</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_INVALID_PARTNAME1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a part name based on design name '%s'.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>581</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_PARTNAME_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a part name for the reason above.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>582</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_INVALID_REFDESNAME1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a reference designator name based on the import codesign form name '%s'.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>583</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_REFDESNAME_ERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a reference designator name for the reason above.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>584</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_NETERROR</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not component net(s) for reason above.   
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
       <Id>585</Id>
       <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_NETWARN1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
       <Category>W</Category>
       <Desc>
Could not create package net for IC net '%s', skipping to next net.
       </Desc>
       <Output>C</Output>
       <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
       <Id>586</Id>
       <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_NETUSE2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
       <Category>W</Category>
       <Desc>
Power net '%s' does not specify whether it is Power or Ground, and is being assigned a voltage value %f.
       </Desc>
       <Output>C</Output>
       <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>587</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_COMPINST_PROPS_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not add component instance properties for the reason above.   
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>588</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_COMPDEF_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not add component definition for the reason above.   
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>589</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_FUNCDEFNAME1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a functional definition name based on slot name '%s'.   
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>590</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_COMPINST_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a component instance for the reason above.   
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>591</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_CHK_PINNAME1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
An invalid pin name was detected for pin '%s'.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>592</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_CHK_PINNUMBER1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
An invalid pin number was detected for pin '%s'.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>593</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_SYMDEF_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a symbol definition for the reason above.  
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>594</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_SYMINST_FAILED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Could not create a symbol instance for the reason above.  
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>595</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSAMSG_NOT_SIP_DESIGN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Internal: a DSA API function was called that is only appropriate for SIP/DPS designs containing die-stacks.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
   </Msg>

   <Msg>
        <Id>596</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_DUPLICATE_DIE1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
Found an existing component '%s'. Use a die abstract with a unique design name.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
   </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>597</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPEXCELMSG_INVALID_KEY_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
%s is not a recognized (or currently supported) property name for this field.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
For a complete listing of the properties and their values that are accepted in an
Excel Spreadsheet XML file, please refer to the Microsoft documentation for the
SpreadsheetML format online.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>598</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPEXCELMSG_INVALID_KEY_VALUE_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
%s is not a recognized value for the %s property for this field.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
For a complete listing of the properties and their values that are accepted in an
Excel Spreadsheet XML file, please refer to the Microsoft documentation for the
SpreadsheetML format online.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>599</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPEXCELMSG_INVALID_VALUE_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
%s is not a recognized value for this field of the Excel XML format.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
For a complete listing of the properties and their values that are accepted in an
Excel Spreadsheet XML file, please refer to the Microsoft documentation for the
SpreadsheetML format online.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>600</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPEXCELMSG_SKILL_UNKNOWN_PROP_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
%s is not a recognized value for this field of the spreadsheet XML format.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>601</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPEXCELMSG_SKILL_NOT_ACTIVE_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
No spreadsheet %s is active. Value not set.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>602</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPEXCELMSG_SKILL_NOT_DEFINED_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Unable to create requested %s for active spreadsheet.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>603</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPEXCELMSG_SKILL_BAD_CELLPOS_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Illegal cell position defined (%d %d). Row and column must be position integers.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>604</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_SUBCLASS_NOTFOUND_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
%s layer %s not found in drawing. Bond wire not created.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>605</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_STARTEND_NOTFOUND_2</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
No valid %s item found at %s for bond wire to connect to. Bond wire not created.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>606</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_STARTEND_DIFF_NETS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Start and end items are not on the same net (%s and %s). Bond wire not created.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>607</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_BWIMPORT_NUMFAILED_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
%d bond wires could not be created.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>608</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_MISSING_LEFMACRO1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Could not find the Library macro '%s' with a valid pin.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>609</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_MISSING_LEFMACRO</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The required LEF macro specified in the die abstract is missing from the LEF Library. Regenerate the CML file to include the macro with a valid pin.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>610</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_PLUGIN_LIBDEFS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The current OpenAccess software has the cds.lib plug-in installed, but a library definition file named 'lib.defs' has been selected in the current directory. Migrate this lib.defs file to cds.lib file to avoid this warning.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>611</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_NOPLUGIN_CDSLIB</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      The current OpenAccess software does not have the cds.lib plug-in installed, but a library definition file named 'cds.lib' has been selected in the current directory. Not all constructs in the cds.lib file may be supported. If errors occur while reading the cds.lib file, either install the cds.lib plug-in, or remove the statements from the cds.lib file that are non-conforming.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>612</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_PLUGIN_BOTH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      The current OpenAccess software has the cds.lib plug-in installed and both cds.lib and lib.defs files are present in the current directory. The cds.lib file will be used. The lib.defs file will be ignored and it will not be updated.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>613</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_NOPLUGIN_BOTH</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      The current OpenAccess software does not have the cds.lib plug-in installed and both lib.defs and cds.lib files are present in the current directory. The lib.defs file will be used. The cds.lib file will be ignored and it will not be updated.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>614</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_CON_TEMP_VIEW</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
sipTempView cannot be selected as a view for adding a codesign die. sipTempView is a reserved view name for die editor operations to store changes made in IO Planner. sipTempView is created when Update Package is invoked in IO Planner. Choose the view name 'layout' to avoid this warning.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>615</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_NOT_AVAILABLE_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
%s requires the "Chip Integration" product option. Use the File -> Change Editor command to enable this option and run the command again.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>
   <Msg>
        <Id>616</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_USE_DIA_LIB</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>
            I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
            Library Data read from .dia file will be used.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>617</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_USE_LIB_CML</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>
            I
            <Sub-Category>P</Sub-Category>
        </Category>
        <Desc>
            Library Data from .cml file created based on the .dia file will be used.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>618</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_CODESIGN_DIE_ACCURACY</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The current database units / accuracy combination is lower than recommended. A minimum of microns with 3 decimal places is strongly advised for IC-package co-design. This can be changed on the Design tab of the Setup -> Design Parameters command. Proceed?
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>
    
   <Msg>
    <Id>619</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_OPTIONS_WRONG_PORT_CLASS1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
Macro %s of class COVER BUMP has a pin with an invalid port class of CORE. Port class will be ignored.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
   
    <Msg>
        <Id>620</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_COVER_BUMP_HAS_CPT_PIN1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
Macro %s of class COVER BUMP has a connection point pin. Connection point pins for COVER BUMP macros are not supported in the current release.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>621</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_COVER_BUMP_NO_DIE_PIN1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
Macro %s of class COVER BUMP does not have a die pin. Macro is invalid and will be ignored.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>622</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_COVER_BUMP_MORE_THEN_ONE_DIE_PIN1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
Macro %s of class COVER BUMP has more then one die pin. Only the first die pin will be considered.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>623</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ACDMSG_DEF_MATCH_TOPCELL</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>E</Category>
        <Desc>
DEF design name must match the cell name from the Verilog file. 
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>624</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_FINGER_FAIL_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
Bond finger creation failed for finger on line %d.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>625</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_EMPTY_TAG_VALUE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
Encountered tag %s in the die abstract that has an empty value. Tags with empty values should be removed from the source abstract file.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>626</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_MACRO_NOT_STUGGER_BUMP1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
Macro %s mentioned in stagger pin section of a pin. This macro if not defined as stagger bump macro.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>
    <Msg>
        <Id>627</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_OLD_CML_STAGGER3</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
The version of the CML file %s is %f. By usisg the IC Library Manager to re-create the CML file and this will update it to version %f to take advantage of stagger bumps and pins information in the library.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

    <Msg>
        <Id>628</Id>
        <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPGENMSG_STACKED_SYM_CAV_OUTLINE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
        <Category>W</Category>
        <Desc>
The cavity outline in the library symbol definition of %s will not be used when placed as a die, spacer, or interposer.
        </Desc>
        <Output>C</Output>
        <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
    </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>629</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPEXCELMSG_BAD_CELL_DATA</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Cell contents must be a string or number.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>630</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPEXCELMSG_PARENT_STYLE_NOT_FOUND_1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Specified parent style %s not defined for spreadsheet.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
    <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>631</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>DSAMSG_FLIP_CHIP_LAYER_CHANGE_3</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
Flip-chip %s has been moved from layer %s to layer %s to match die stack cavity/substrate placement settings.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
A flip-chip die component needs to have its pads on either a package substrate layer, such as the 
top or bottom layer (or an internal layer if the die stack is placed in a cavity). It may only be
placed on a DIESTACK type layer outside the substrate if it sits above another die or interposer
symbol which provides pads for the flip-chip to connect to and a means of connectivity from those
pads to the substrate. 

For this reason, if you create a flip-chip die as the bottom object (closest to the substrate) of a 
die stack, its pads will automatically move to the appropriate substrate layer based on the die stack's
configured surface / cavity placement settings.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>632</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_SUBSTRATE_LAYER_ILLEGAL_PAD</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
One or more multi-layer padstack definitions have pads outside the selected top or bottom layer. Correct these pad definitions before reconfiguring the substrate. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Id>633</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_PINNUM_HAS_CHANGED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
One or more pin numbers have changed. See import log for details.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
    <Id>634</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPMSG_PINNAME_HAS_CHANGED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
One or more pin names have changed. See import log for details.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>

<Msg>
    <Id>635</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CSFG_NO_PINS</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
The are no pins selected for the die. Choose correct layer for pins geometry, press Find Pins button. Symbol will not be created.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
</Msg>

<Msg>
    <Id>636</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CSFG_NO_DIE_OUTLINE</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
The die outline is not defined. Pin outline will be used to create die outline.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
</Msg>

<Msg>
    <Id>637</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>CSFG_PIN_USE_INVALID1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
Pin Use of pin %s is invalid. Choose valid pin use.
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
</Msg>

<Msg>
    <Id>638</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICPOAMSG_DUPLICATE_LAYER1</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
There are more than one layer with layer name %s in the layer section of the IC Library. 
    </Desc>
    <Output>C</Output>
</Msg>
<Msg>
  <Id>640</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_PINNAME_TAG_UNEXPECTED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>W</Category>
  <Desc>
    Encountered a NAME tag with value %s in the die pin section of bump instance %s in the die abstract. Bumps should not contain this tag. This tag will removed from any die abstract generated from this design.
  </Desc>
  <Output>C</Output>
  <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
</Msg>
<Msg>
  <Id>641</Id>
  <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>ICDXMLMSG_PINNAME_TAG_EXPECTED</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
  <Category>W</Category>
  <Desc>
    Instance %s has a die pin record that is missing at NAME tag. This tag is required to associate a pin of the instance to the proper die pin record.
  </Desc>
  <Output>C</Output>
  <CDNUSR_OUTPUT>TEXT_LEVEL</CDNUSR_OUTPUT>
</Msg>
  <Msg>
    <Id>642</Id>
    <CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>PTIWMSG_CODESIGN_PIN</CDNUSR_DEFINE_NAME>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      Pin %s.%s belongs to a co-design object. The pin was not added to net %s.
    </Desc>
    <ExtDesc>
      This error typically occurs when the case of the pin number referenced
      in the text file belongs to a co-design object in the database
      to which it refers.
    </ExtDesc>
    <Output>C</Output>
  </Msg>  
</MsgFile>
