<MsgFile>
  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      "Error Message from ACNSUI_SMI."
    </Desc>
    <Id>1</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      Warning Message from ACNSUI_SMI with 3 params %d %s %s
    </Desc>
    <Id>2</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>I</Category>
    <Desc>
      Information Message from ACNSUI_SMI with 3 INT params %d %d %d
    </Desc>
    <Id>3</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>Q</Category>
    <Desc>
	Question Message from ACNSUI_SMI with 3 INT params %d %d %d \n\r It's a very \r\n long message I put.
It includes tabs \t*\t*\t*\t* and new line \n\n\nI want 
to tab	tab	tab 
see how output string will be formated.
    </Desc>
    <Id>4</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      Selected formula type does not match the current cell.  Use the Formula Browser to select a different formula or continue editing the current formula.
    </Desc>
    <Id>5</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Name is not defined.  Specify name and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Id>6</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Name cannot contain spaces.  Fix name and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Id>7</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      New User-Defined %s name is in use.  Specify different name and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Id>8</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>Q</Category>
    <Desc>
      Parameters are not defined.  Do you want to proceed without parameters?  Select Yes to create a predicate that does not take any parameters.  Select No to return to the Setup dialog to add parameters.
    </Desc>
    <Id>9</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Return type is not defined.  Specify return type and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Id>10</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Object kinds are not selected.  Specify object kinds and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Id>11</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Cannot create function&apos;s prototype.  Check all fields in dialog.
    </Desc>
    <Id>12</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Parameter name is not defined.  Specify parameter name and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Id>13</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Parameter name contains invalid character &apos;%c&apos;.  Valid characters are: A-Z, a-z, 0-9, and &apos;_&apos;.
    </Desc>
    <Id>14</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Data type is not defined.  Select data type from the list and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Id>15</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>Q</Category>
    <Desc>
      Contents have been modified, do you want to save changes?  Press &quot;Yes&quot; to save changes and exit, &quot;No&quot; to exit without saving changes, &quot;Cancel&quot; to continue editing.
    </Desc>
    <Id>16</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>Q</Category>
    <Desc>
      Contents have been modified.  Data modification will be lost.  Would you like to continue?
    </Desc>
    <Id>17</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Error opening file %s.
    </Desc>
    <Id>18</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>Q</Category>
    <Desc>
      %s already exists.  Do you wish to overwrite?
    </Desc>
    <Id>19</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>Q</Category>
    <Desc>
      Text formatting and comments for the text will be lost.  Would you like to continue?
    </Desc>
    <Id>20</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      User-Defined %s name is not defined.  Use &quot;Edit Params...&quot; button to launch Setup dialog and specify name.
    </Desc>
    <Id>21</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      User-Defined %s return type is not defined.  Use &quot;Edit Params...&quot; button to launch Setup dialog and specify return type.
    </Desc>
    <Id>22</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Cannot create Measurement&apos;s prototype.  Check all fields in dialog.
    </Desc>
    <Id>23</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>Q</Category>
    <Desc>
      No measurements currently exist that match the data type of the attribute.  Do you wish to create a new measurement?  Select Yes to create a new measurement.  Select No to return to the previous dialog.
    </Desc>
    <Id>24</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Measurement is not selected.  Select measurement from the list or press Cancel button.
    </Desc>
    <Id>25</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Could not create log file for Test.  Disk might be full or directory might not be writable.  Check disk capacity and permissions on working directory.
    </Desc>
    <Id>26</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Could not create temporary file for Skill Lint check.  Disk might be full or directory might not be writable.  Check disk capacity and permissions on working directory.
    </Desc>
    <Id>27</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      No item selected from the list.  Make selection and press &quot;OK&quot; button.
    </Desc>
    <Id>28</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Parameter value %s is not an integer.  Value contains illegal characters.  Check parameter value and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Id>29</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>E</Category>
    <Desc>
      Parameter value %s is not a real.  Value contains illegal characters.  Check parameter value and try again.
    </Desc>
    <Id>30</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>
  
  <Msg>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      Current measurement allows objects to have multiple parents.  This can not be specified by the Select Objects dialog.  Fill in the parameter values individually to run the test.
    </Desc>
    <Id>31</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      Deleting measurement %s will cause any Actuals that use this measurement to fail analysis.
      
      Select OK to delete measurement %s, select Cancel to keep it.
    </Desc>
    <Id>32</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      Deleting predicate %s will cause errors in any formula, predicate, or measurement that calls it.
      
      Select OK to delete predicate %s, select Cancel to keep it.
    </Desc>
    <Id>33</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <Msg>
    <Category>W</Category>
    <Desc>
      Delete all formulas from the current design that are not in use.
      Deleted formulas will not be available for assignment to constraints.
      
      Select OK to delete formulas, select Cancel to quit.
    </Desc>
    <Id>34</Id>
    <Output>U</Output>
  </Msg>

  <LogFile>"acnsui.log"
  </LogFile>

  <CharsPerLine>  50
  </CharsPerLine>

</MsgFile>
